

Md. Rohul Amin

Software Engineer

Sha 66/3, Shadhinata Sarani, North Badda, Gulshan, Dhaka, Bangladesh ## 05 Jan 1996

🟲 Bangladeshi 🕲 Unmarried in radipu 🞧 radipu 🖺 radipu 🕲 dipuxoo Bē radipu

radipu.me 🖒 radipu

CAREER OBJECTIVES

I am a graduate with a bachelor's degree in Computer Science and Engineering. I am experienced in both front-end and back-end programming languages. Now, I am looking for establishing my career as a .NET developer. I am a quick learner and willing to learn new technologies to upgrade myself with time. I am working with .NET technology since 2018.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Jan 2022 **Software Engineer**Dhaka, Bangladesh CureTech Ltd

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022Software EngineerSunderland, EnglandGinilab Limited ☑

Ginilab is a software development company based in Sunderland, Tyne & Wear, UK. Over the last few years, they've made a reputation for building software that looks great and is easy to use. Currently, I worked there with .NET Framework, DevExpress, WinForms, Software Design, Fronend, and Back-end.

Feb 2021 – Jul 2021 Software Engineer

Dhaka, Bangladesh OurEdu

OurEdu provides web-based software for educational institutions. I have had working here with C# ASP.NET Core 3.1, JavaScript, Bootstrap, iOuery, LINO CSS MSSOL DevOps

jQuery, LINQ, CSS, MSSQL, DevOps.

Jan 2015 - Jan 2021 **Head of Information and Communication Technology**Dhaka, Bangladesh Bangladesh Study Forum (BDSF) 🗷

This is a non-profit organization. I developed the whole IT system in this organization. Currently, if the organization needs any IT solution, I consult them with IT support. This is neither a full-time job nor a part-time one. I barely give time in this organization only when they need me.

What have I done: Website development, Organized programs, public speaking, Leadership.

PROJECTS

Feb 2022 - present Bachao ☑

Against the rape

It's a mobile application platform where a victim can seek help during and after the incident. The backend was developed with .NET.

Technology Used: .NET5, Angular, WebAPI, MSSQL

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022 Restaurant Management System

It's a desktop software, mostly used in the UK and in the middle east. Nearly 200+ restaurants and thousands of customers use this software

for ordering food inside and outside the restaurant.

Technology Used: ASP.NET, DevExpress, WinForms, MySQL, Laragon,

HeidiSQL

Feb 2021 - May 2021 Account Management System for Shidlai Ashraf Secondary

School

Technology Used: C#, ASP.NET Core 3.1, JavaScript, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, JSON, LINQ, and following by Onion Architecture.

May 2019 - Aug 2019 Library Management System

Technology Used: C#, ASP.NET Core 2.1, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, JSON,

LINQ.

SKILLS

Programming

Language

C, C++, Java, JavaScript, C#, R, Python,

TypeScript, Go

Backend

Development

.NET Core, .NET, NodeJS, Laravel

DevOps

AWS, GCP, Azure, Docker, Jenkins, Kubernetes,

Bash

Data Structure and —

Algorithm

Cyber Security

Penetration, Forensics, Reverse Engineering, Social Engineering **Frontend**

Development

VueJS, Angular, HTML5, AngularJS,

Bootstrap3, 4, CSS3, Sass

Database

Oracle, MySQL, MSSQL Server, PostgreSQL

Source Control

Git, GitHub

Interpersonal skills -

Listening, Caring, Leadership, Self-Motivated,

Responsibility, Teamwork

EDUCATION

May 2021 Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering

Dhaka, Bangladesh International University of Business Agriculture and Technology

Completed BSc with a CGPA of 3.27 out of 4.00

Jul 2011 - Aug 2013 Higher Secondary Certificate

Dhaka, Bangladesh Cambrian College

Completed HSC with a GPA of 5.00 out of 5.00

Jan 2009 - May 2011 Secondary School Certificate

Cumilla, Bangladesh Shidlai Ashraf Secondary School

Completed SSC with a GPA of 5.00 out of 5.00

♂ INTERESTS

Learning New Skills
Public Speaking
Reading

Writing

♦ LANGUAGES

Bangla • • • • • English • • • • •